Bonus Short Stories

During Hide and Seek

One day in the spirit folk village...

Around here should do.

Rio was playing hide and seek with the village children in the square. He sat behind a random tree and made himself as small as possible, then controlled his breathing so that he wouldn’t be discovered easily. That being said, there were werebeast children who had strong senses of smell. Rio could technically use spirit arts to befuddle the noses of werebeasts, but they were just children, and it wouldn’t be mature of him to go all-out against them. It would only be a matter of time until he was discovered —

“Found you, Onii-chan.”

Latifa appeared out of nowhere and sat down beside Rio, then hugged him tightly to prevent him from running away.

“You’re not the one looking, Latifa.”

“Ehehe, I wanted to hide together with Onii-chan,” Latifa confessed earnestly.

“I see. Then let’s hope they don’t find us.”

“Yup.”

Rio laughed gently and hugged Latifa softly by the shoulder. Latifa nodded happily in return and tightened her hold around him.

“Being together outside like this reminds me of when we used to travel together, heading for the village,” Latifa suddenly said.

“Yeah,” Rio nodded with a chuckle.

Back then, whenever they had a break or stopped for food, Latifa would stick closely to Rio just like this. She would take every chance she got to do so — not that she was any different now, but still.

“Fufu, Onii-chan’s scent makes me feel safe. I love it!” Latifa buried her face into Rio’s chest, rubbing her cheek against him.

She’s grown bigger, but she’s still affectionately spoiled, huh? Rio patted Latifa’s head gently with an amused smile on his face.

Little Witch Rikka’s Invitation?!

The high school Amakawa Haruto attended was a prep school that had both middle school and high school divisions. The high school division consisted of those who moved up from the middle school division, as well as those who tested in from outside.

One day in the middle of fall, the middle school division held their school festival ahead of the high school division. All kinds of events and stalls were taking place in the middle school grounds, attracting many visitors from both schools, as well as residents nearby; it was bustling with activity.

However, there was one female student who had slipped over to the high school side, seeking a moment of peace. The girl’s name was Minamoto Rikka, a third-year middle school student.

“Phew, I’m beat.” Rikka sat down on a bench and stretched her arms with a light sigh. She had been working as a waitress for her class’s Halloween-themed cafe.

In the spirit of the cafe’s theme, Rikka wore a light blue wig and a witch outfit. The skirt was rather short and the shirt emphasized her chest a little, attracting curious gazes from people while she walked to her current location.

“Huh, what a coincidence. What are you doing here?”

Two older boys appeared out of nowhere, and one of them called out to Rikka.

“...Who are you? You’re not students from here, right?” Rikka replied to the boys rather cautiously.

“Oh, there’s no need to be so wary. We were at your store as customers, and we spotted you by chance just now,” one of the boys said smoothly, as though he had prepared those words in advance. But they were quite far from the middle school grounds; it wasn’t a place that was so easy to wander to by coincidence.

Did they follow me? Rikka wondered.

“I see. Bye, then.” Rikka immediately stood up from the bench and strode off. Without missing a beat, the boys began to walk along with her, sandwiching her between them.

“Hold up. We just wanted to be friends with you. What’s your number? Ah, you should show us around the festival if you have time. The name’s Sakata, by the way.”

“Sorry. I have things to deal with.” Rikka quickened her pace in an attempt to leave the boys behind.

“But you were sitting on the bench just now, right?” the boy said, having observed Rikka’s actions before.

Ugh, how annoying.

Just as Rikka was getting fed up —

“Ah, there you are. I was looking for you.”

From a slight distance away, a male student from the high school division called out to Rikka.

“Ah? And who are you?” Unhappy, the boys spoke menacingly to the newcomer.

“I’m a student from the high school division, and I was searching for her. ...Do you know these people? The teacher will be here soon, so if there’s any trouble, I’ll speak up as a witness,” the male student replied undauntedly, hinting at the presence of a teacher.

“Wha? N-No, we were just asking for directions.” The boy seemed to be intimidated, as his voice cracked when he answered.

“The middle school building is that way.” The male student smiled and pointed at the path that led back to the middle school division.

“Yeah. Let’s go.” The boys promptly retreated towards the middle school grounds, leaving Rikka alone with the male student who had appeared.

“T-Thank you very much, Amakawa-senpai,” Rikka sighed in relief and thanked the boy — Amakawa Haruto.

“...Sorry, have we met before?” Haruto tilted his head curiously. He didn’t recall ever meeting Rikka before.

“Ah! N-No, you’re just famous among the middle schoolers! That’s why I know your name, s-sorry!” Rikka apologized in a panic.

“It’s nothing to apologize for... But, am I really famous?” Haruto’s eyes widened.

“U-Umm, it’s just that one of my friends likes you, so...” Rikka explained rather awkwardly.

“...O-Oh. I see. Sorry for asking,” Haruto apologized hesitantly.

“N-No! I’m the one who’s sorry!” said Rikka.

An awkward silence fell between the two of them. Then, after a beat...

“...Shall I walk you back to the middle school?” Haruto suggested. “You might run into those people again on your way back.”

“Thank you very much. I-If you don’t mind, then please. Ah, our class is doing a cafe, so please come visit! I’d like to thank you for your help just now anyway!” Rikka bowed her head shyly.

Chapter 1: Atonement

Outside of Amande’s city walls, in the location where Rio and Lucius had been battling it out mere moments ago, Rio and Flora now stood closely facing each other.

“U-Umm, Sir Rio...” Flora clutched Rio’s sleeve and whispered his name quietly.

“Yes.” Without breaking eye contact, Rio nodded with a guilty look, but his heart wasn’t present. After a moment, he slowly looked up at the sun rising in the distant sky. Unreachable and bright, it was like something to be yearned for...

Flora gently tugged the sleeve of Rio’s shirt, asking once again, “Sir Rio... You’re Sir Rio, aren’t you?”

“...” Rio looked back down at Flora as though he had been dragged back to reality. But he didn’t speak, instead frowning in thought at how to deal with the current situation.

Haruto, is everything okay? At the same time, Aishia’s telepathy echoed in Rio’s head.

...Yeah, it’s fine. Rio calmed himself, and replied to Aishia. I’m just a little busy right now. Can you contact me later?

Got it. He heard Aishia’s immediate response before the telepathy cut off. Once it did, Rio finally opened his mouth to speak.

“...Who might you be referring to?” He stared at Flora’s face and feigned ignorance.

An extremely saddened look crossed Flora’s face before she was enraged by the answer that didn’t meet her expectations. “Y-You, you’re S-S-Sir Rio! Just now, that man said so — that you’re Rio!” she said in frustration.

“...I was once called that, yes. I have the name of Rio in addition to my name of Haruto. But why are you calling me by such a name, Princess Flora?” Rio cocked his head and asked with an utmost look of curiosity, as though implying the Rio that Flora knew was someone else.

“...Mm...” Flora felt like she had been strongly rejected, and her face twisted with tears.

“I currently live by the public name of Haruto. Pardon my rudeness in asking so, but I would be extremely grateful if you could forget what you heard earlier.” Rio cut to the chase with his request without any further explanation.

“N-No, I don’t want to!” Flora clung to Rio’s chest like a lost child.

Chapter 4: Your Shadow

Once Rio, Celia, and Aishia left Amande through the east gate, they proceeded walking east down the main road. After some time passed, they confirmed that no one was around them before taking off into the sky. They continued through the air towards Galtuuk, the capital of the Kingdom of Galarc, and arrived at the outskirts of the capital before sunset. After they’d searched the rocky areas of the outskirts for somewhere isolated, they set up the rock house.

Celia sat down on the living room sofa and stretched. “It feels like it’s been a while since I’ve lived in this house.”

“We only stayed for a few days, but a lot happened in our time at Amande.” Rio placed the tea he had prepared down on the table and agreed with a smile of amusement.

“...Yeah. It feels kind of strange. I’ve only lived in this house for a short time, but it feels like I’ve come home,” Celia said keenly.

“Thank you for saying that. Maybe it’s because there’s no one else around, so you can mentally relax,” Rio guessed.

“Yeah, that must be it.” Celia nodded bashfully.

“Also because we can start taking baths again, and eating meals together with Haruto,” Aishia interrupted. Celia giggled, agreeing along happily.

“Ah, that’s true — you’re right there. I look forward to that.”

“I have to leave for a while starting tomorrow, so we’ll only be able to eat together tonight and tomorrow morning, but I’ll put my everything into cooking tonight. Professor, Aishia, you can relax and take a bath in the meantime,” Rio suggested to the two of them.

“...Mm, that’s a tempting idea, but could you teach me how to cook tonight? You promised me before, remember?” Celia asked, her cheeks turned a faint shade of crimson.

“Of course. I don’t mind at all, but wouldn’t you rather we do it at a less rushed time?” If she was cooking for the first time, it’d be better to learn continuously for a few days in a row. Rio would be leaving tomorrow, so there wasn’t much he could teach in just one lesson.

“Nope. I’ll be living together with Aishia while you’re gone. Aishia can cook some simple foods, but I should be able to make at least one thing myself, right? And I can practice while you’re gone too,” Celia said in slight embarrassment.

“...I understand. Then, let’s see if I can teach you some simple recipes,” Rio suggested with a gentle smile.

“Yup!” Celia responded happily, and the three of them made dinner together that night.

◇　◇　◇

The next morning, as Rio prepared to depart for the village...

“I’ll be going now,” he said after he’d stepped out of the rock house. “I’ll be gone for two weeks, so please look after each other.” He looked at Aishia as he spoke to Celia.

“Of course. Leave Aishia to me,” Celia said proudly.

“Will do. You take care too, Aishia,” Rio said with a chuckle.

“...Got it,” Aishia said, before suddenly hugging Rio.

“Wha?!” Rio himself was surprised, but Celia was even more surprised than him. Her eyes were round as she watched Aishia hug Rio dumbfoundedly.

“What’s wrong, Aishia?” Rio asked Aishia quietly. While the two of them were always close to each other, this was the first time they had hugged like this.

“No matter how far we’re separated or where Haruto is heading towards, I will always be with you. So don’t fear, don’t falter, and go down the path that you choose,” Aishia said in a rare show of talkativeness. Her words were rather hesitant and vague, but Rio could make a guess at why she had chosen to speak like this. It was most likely because Rio had fulfilled his fated reunion with Lucius in such an unexpected way.

“...There’s nothing that gets past you, Aishia. Thanks,” Rio said a little awkwardly with a faint smile.

Ever since his fight with Lucius, the desire for revenge had been boiling intensely within Rio’s chest. Despite that, he had thought he had been behaving normally to those around him, but there was no fooling the one his soul was bound to. While it was a little awkward to have his own heart seen through so easily, it also felt comfortable for some reason. Rio obediently entrusted himself to Aishia’s embrace, but Celia returned to her senses with a gasp and spoke up in a panic. “H-Hey, hey! How long are you going to be hugging for?! That’s so unfair — let go already! I can’t let my guard down at all around you!”

“Okay.” Rio nodded in amusement and slowly distanced himself from Aishia.

“I was just saying my farewells. Aren’t you going to do that, Celia?” Aishia cocked her head sideways.

“N... R-Right. You’ll be gone for a while, s-so I guess...” Celia reflexively tried to decline, but then blushed as she agreed reluctantly.

“Well...” Rio tried to object, but Celia began to approach. Since he had been certain Celia would be too flabbergasted to do anything, Rio swallowed his words in slight surprise.

“...B-Be careful, Rio. I’ll practice the recipes you taught me and wait here!” With a bright red face, Celia hugged Rio with all her might. Celia’s body was small, but warm.

“...Yes. I’ll be back soon.” Rio smiled a little uncomfortably and returned Celia’s hug.

◇　◇　◇

Rio moved a small distance away from the rock house and took out the teleport crystal. He could have used it in front of Celia, but if he did he could imagine how her panicked eyes would search Aishia for an explanation. Even if he told her about it beforehand, the discussion would’ve become pretty long-winded.

“Transilio.” Rio chanted the spell and activated the teleport crystal in his hand. The air distorted and warped around the teleport crystal, vanishing Rio into thin air. In the next moment the forest surrounding the village filled his vision. His teleportation was successful.

“I’m sure someone will come here if I just wait, but...” He decided to approach the village himself this time. Kicking off the ground, Rio rose into the air with spirit arts and moved across the forest. The buildings of the village were lined in rows just below him, and towering past them was the giant tree that was Dryas’ main body. Rio flew along leisurely, heading for the tree where the village’s town hall was located — which was large, but nothing compared to the size of Dryas’ tree. Before long, a large bird rose into the sky from the ground. It was Ariel, Orphia’s contracted spirit.

“Onii-chan!”

And the first one to welcome Rio was, as expected, Latifa. As an adopted sister, she didn’t want to give up that role to anyone else. Riding on the back of Ariel, she waved her arms enthusiastically from a dozen or so meters away. Orphia and Miharu were also on Ariel’s back.

When Rio first spotted Latifa, his mouth softened in a smile, but when he spotted Miharu next, his face clouded faintly.

Miharu...

He averted his eyes; he couldn’t look at her directly. She was so bright, it felt like someone had a stranglehold on his chest.

“...?” Miharu noticed that Rio had averted his eyes and made a worried face. She continued staring at Rio’s face after that, but he still refused to meet her gaze. In the meantime, Rio and Ariel made contact midair.

“Welcome back, Onii-chan!” Latifa called out with a beaming smile.

“...I’ve returned, Latifa. You look like you’ve been well,” Rio replied with a gentle smile on his face.

“Yup!” Latifa nodded energetically.

“It’s nice to see you again too, Orphia, Miharu. I’m not used to the sight of having the two of you come out to greet me; it’s rather unexpected,” Rio said to the two of them, somewhat shyly. This time, he was able to give his usual warm smile to Miharu without averting his gaze.

“Is that so? While you were gone from the village, we became really close friends. Isn’t that right, Miharu?” Orphia giggled.

“Yup. We’re always together, after all,” Miharu said with a happy laugh. Perhaps the averted eye contact with Rio earlier was just her imagination...

“Say, Onii-chan. Can I jump over there?” Latifa pleaded restlessly, seemingly without the patience to wait until they arrived on the ground.

“Of course not — it’s dangerous. It’s just a little longer until we reach the ground. Be patient,” Rio admonished Latifa with a wry smile.

“Hmph, why can’t we go faster?” Latifa puffed up her cheeks a little and looked downwards. The town hall was already right before their eyes as the group slowly descended past it.

“Come to think of it, I don’t see Lady Aishia with you...” Orphia said.

“Aishia’s watching over the house back in Strahl.”

“Oh, really?” Orphia’s eyes widened.

“Yes. The teacher I am indebted to is actually under my protection right now, so we’re living together. She’s staying back to look after her, like an escort.”

“That indebted teacher is the one you mentioned before, right? The woman who was five years older. Her name was Celia, if I recall correctly?” Orphia asked. Latifa’s fluffy fox ears twitched when she heard that Rio was living with a young woman. However, she didn’t make any moves to interrupt their talk.

Rio’s eyes widened slightly. “Yes. You have a good memory.”

“Fufu. Of course I’d remember — it was something we discussed together. But that aside, why are you back this time? It hasn’t been that long since you last left...” Orphia said slightly bashfully, before tilting her head and changing the subject.

Rio looked at Miharu. “I’ve found the whereabouts of Miharu’s upperclassman, Sumeragi Satsuki. I wanted to report that and discuss my plans for the future, if possible.”

“...You found... Satsuki...” Miharu must have been quite shocked, as she was blinking with a blank look on her face.

“First I will go inform the head elders of my return, but then I’d like to have Aki and Masato join my explanation of the situation. Where are they right now?” Rio asked.

“Ah, I think they’re training with Sara and Alma right now,” Miharu answered with a gasp.

“But Sara and the others must have realized that Onii-chan’s returned, so maybe they’re heading towards the town hall already?” Latifa added.

“That’s true,” Orphia agreed. “I think we should just head to the town hall like this,” she said, gesturing for Rio to continue descending.

“I understand. Actually, I see them now.” Rio looked down at the square in front of the town hall and smiled when he spotted Sara and the others. A short time later, they reached the ground.

Latifa immediately went to hug Rio. “Once again, welcome home, Onii-chan!”

“Good to be back, Latifa. I’m glad to see you all look well, too, Sara.” Rio caught Latifa’s body with a smiling huff, then looked at Sara, who had come running over earlier.

“Welcome back, Rio.” Sara greeted Rio with a lively voice, either from running over or out of happiness at seeing Rio again. However, she wasn’t out of breath. Sara hadn’t endured all her tough training just to be out of breath from a little jog. Which meant the reason for her lively voice became obvious enough.

It was at that point that Alma finally appeared, dashing over with Masato and Aki in tow. Alma wasn’t particularly out of breath either, but Masato and Aki were huffing slightly.

“Sara was so fast, we could barely keep up,” Alma said tiredly while shooting Sara a look.

“Honestly. We have enough trouble as is running fast without magic artifacts,” Masato agreed with a grin.

“Ahaha,” Aki laughed in amusement, looking at Sara.

“Fufu, is that so? Why were you in such a rush, Sara?” Orphia asked, also laughing.

“I-I just didn’t want to lose sight of Rio, so I ran ahead of everyone to catch him first and wait for the others,” Sara answered in a high-pitched voice, having placed a strong emphasis on the fact that she’d done so for everyone’s sake.

“Geez, even if you didn’t hurry he would have waited. Right, Rio?” Orphia asked, turning to address Rio.

“Yes, there was something I wanted to tell Aki and Masato too, after all,” Rio said calmly with a nod.

“...To us?” Aki and Masato exchanged glances and looked at him in confusion.

“I’ve found Satsuki’s location.”

“R-Really?! What about my brother?!” Aki stammered, being the first to react right away.

“Unfortunately, I still haven’t been able to locate your older brother...”

“I-Is that so...” Aki’s shoulders slumped in disappointment.

“But now that we know Satsuki is here, it’s almost certain that your brother is in this world too. So far, all the heroes have been affiliated with a kingdom without exception, so I think it’s more than plausible.” While being affiliated with a kingdom brought up more problems in itself, Rio had said that to cheer up Aki. Latifa watched their exchange closely while still clinging to Rio.

“...Yes. Just knowing where Satsuki is makes me happy. It might be possible that my brother and Satsuki are together, or something,” Aki thought optimistically.

“That’s true. For now, I’d like to go to the head elders to make my report, so let’s continue discussing this there,” Rio suggested with a small smile.

“Yes!” Aki agreed enthusiastically. Meanwhile, Miharu had been staring at Rio’s side profile as he conversed with Aki.

“...” Her memories were vague and indistinct, but that dream she saw the other day... She couldn’t forget it. It was the trigger that caused her to strongly overlap this man and her childhood friend.

“What’s wrong, Miharu? ...Miharu?” Because Latifa was clinging onto Rio, she felt the gaze Miharu had directed to him and called out to her.

“...Eh? What?” Miharu snapped back to her senses and tilted her head awkwardly.

“Nothing, you were just watching Onii-chan in a daze...” Latifa said, giving Miharu a searching look. Rio and the others were also drawn in by Latifa’s words and looked at Miharu.

“Ah, really? Was I doing that?” Miharu noticed that attention was gathering on her and ducked her head uncomfortably.

“...Oh, was it because you wanted to hug Onii-chan too, Miharu?” Latifa asked in a bright voice. At that, Sara, Orphia, and Alma all looked at Miharu with great interest.

“Huh? ...Ah, no, that’s...” Miharu was taken aback, her body shaking with a flinch. When her eyes met Rio’s, she hid her face to avoid his gaze.

“Hey, Latifa. Don’t go picking on Miharu,” Rio warned her with a wry smile.

“...Okay!” Latifa agreed obediently and turned her gaze to Miharu to observe her expression.

“All right, let’s go then,” Rio urged the party to head towards the head elders.

Sara took the lead and agreed, walking towards the entrance of the town hall. “Yes, let’s.”

Orphia and Alma glanced at Miharu before following her. Similarly, Aki and Masato sent Miharu a look before walking off.

Before he started walking after Sara and the others, Rio stopped and looked down at the girl that still clung to him. “Are you not going to walk by yourself, Latifa?”

“Hmm... Then, can I hold hands with you, Onii-chan?” Latifa asked Rio like a spoiled child. She probably valued every short moment she could spend touching Rio, which was why she could speak so openly to him.

“Yeah, sure.” Rio nodded immediately.

“Yay! Ehehe.” Latifa’s features relaxed as she grabbed Rio’s left hand. Her expression was one of pure bliss.

“...” Miharu stood still as she watched their exchange.

“Shall we go, Latifa?” While Rio noticed Miharu’s gaze, he chose not to look at her and pulled Latifa’s hand as he walked off. Latifa seemed to sense that and nodded awkwardly as they walked, before looking back.

“Let’s go, Miharu!”

“Ah, yeah. That’s right.” Miharu smiled widely and slowly started walking, but her gaze was still fixed on Rio’s back —

“...Is that you, Haru-kun?” she whispered inaudibly at his back, but her voice must not have reached him, as Rio did not react.

◇　◇　◇

The group headed up to the top floor of the town hall to meet the three head elders of the village. Rio greeted them first, then told them about how he had located Satsuki, just as he had told Miharu and the others already.

“I see — I understand now. So what do you intend on doing, Lord Rio?” High elf Syldora asked Rio.

“In a month and a half’s time, there will be a banquet to officially introduce the existence of the hero, Satsuki. I have actually made a connection with a certain noble that will allow me to attend that banquet.”

“Ah, so you plan on meeting that Satsuki girl at that banquet, then?” Elder dwarf Dominic asked.

“Yes, that is correct,” Rio replied. Ursula, the werefox head elder, looked doubtful.

“...But will it really go so smoothly?”

“It should. The other party is a fairly well-known noble of the Galarc Kingdom, and is aware of my aim to meet Satsuki. My request to accompany them to the banquet was accepted on top of that,” Rio replied.

“I see. Did you tell them about Lady Miharu and the others?” Syldora asked with wide eyes. Rio shook his head slowly.

“No, I’ve kept Miharu’s situation hidden.”

At that, the head elders looked at each other and tilted their heads.

“...It seems like the conditions are rather favorable for you, Lord Rio. Are you sure there is no ulterior motive here?” Syldora asked on behalf of the other head elders.

“While I can’t say for certain, there shouldn’t be. The time we spent together was short, but I believe the noble is intelligent with a strong sense of duty,” Rio said on his impression of Liselotte.

“I see. If you are going that far to describe them, then we shall trust the character of this person too,” Syldora said, smile widening with a chuckle.

“However, this will be a gathering of heroes and human royalty and nobility. There’s no way they would allow you entry for free, no? Just what series of events occurred for you to gain access to the banquet?” Dominic dug a little further in regards to how Rio’s invitation came to be. Despite his rough appearance, he was actually a thoughtful person who didn’t have the role of a head elder for nothing.

“I saved the noble in question during their crisis. I had partially assisted them for that intent, but it seemed like they felt very indebted and made such arrangements in gratitude.”

“I see. So that’s how it is,” Dominic smiled in understanding.

“Knowing your personality, they must have good judgment too,” Ursula said with a small smile. Syldora huffed and smiled, too.

“Well, we can hear more about that later over a drink or two. We now understand the general situation. Based on what you’ve told us, there is no need for us to intervene anywhere for now. Is that correct?” Dominic asked.

“Yes.”

“Indeed.”

Syldora and Ursula both responded immediately.

“That’s how it is. The main players are the young ones, after all. Of course, we’ll give you our opinions if needed, but it would be proper for you to discuss and decide among yourselves. How about that, Rio?” Dominic asked.

“Yes,” Rio agreed. “That was what I intended too. Miharu, what do you think?”

“...I...” Miharu was unable to respond right away, a look of hesitation on her face. She returned the look Rio was giving her, but she bit her lip, at a loss for words.

“I-I want to see her! I want to see Satsuki! It’s possible my brother might be with her, and even if he isn’t, she might know something about him! I have to go and ask!” Aki said.

“Hmm...” Masato seemed to be thinking something, his arms crossed and a contemplative look on his face. Apparently, Aki was the only one with no doubt in her feelings.

“W-What’s the matter, Masato? Don’t you want to see our brother?”

“No, of course I want to see him. It’s just... I’m still in the middle of my sword training, and it doesn’t seem like we can come back that easily if we leave,” Masato said.

“T-That’s...” The look on Aki’s face changed, making her speechless with discomfort. Even Aki didn’t become emotional and say that Masato could continue his sword training elsewhere, because Aki knew that it wasn’t about that. Masato was able to devote himself to his sword training in this village, where he had friends he could compete with. Aki herself had made irreplaceable friends in the village, and she had seen Masato work his hardest on his sword training. He probably didn’t want to fail at it halfway through.

“Anyway, what good would come out of us going? We were brought to this village precisely because we’d get in Haruto’s way, no?” Masato said, making a sound argument.

“That’s true, but...” Aki was at a complete loss for words.

“You wouldn’t be a nuisance at all. It might be difficult, but it’s my job to do something about that. That’s why I want to hear what the three of you truly think,” Rio said in a calming voice. Masato and Aki exchanged glances before bowing their heads to Rio.

“...Thanks.”

“Thank you very much.”

Rio continued, “But there are several conditions attached, so I’ll inform you of those first. After hearing them, take some time thinking about it, discussing it with each other, then give me your answer.”

“O-Okay. What are they?” Masato braced himself and asked.

“First, the major premise of all this is that Satsuki is currently in a position of being a hero affiliated with the Galarc Kingdom — this is basically certain. The problem with being affiliated with a kingdom, however, is that she may not be able to move freely outside, and we can’t just go and meet her easily. You understand this, right?”

By having the hero Satsuki — a disciple of the Six Wise Gods — affiliated with them, the kingdom could increase their own power and influence. Basically, she was a portable idol to worship.

It would be a bad move to upset Satsuki’s mood, so the kingdom probably wouldn’t do anything to provoke her. However, they would still keep Satsuki’s movements under surveillance and indirectly try to manage her. It was hard to believe they would allow her to move freely.

“Yeah, pretty much,” Masato said hesitantly. Aki and Miharu nodded in agreement too.

“I’ve told you about the Six Wise Gods before, right? They’re the gods worshiped in the Strahl region. It wouldn’t be a stretch to say that the royalty in each of the kingdoms of Strahl were formed on the foundation of the Six Wise Gods’ power. Now that the heroes — the disciples of the Six Wise Gods — have descended in each kingdom, they can’t turn a blind eye to such a serious affair. The religious value of the heroes is directly connected to their political value, after all,” Rio explained plainly.

“...” Miharu, Aki, Masato, and the other spirit folk all listened to Rio’s words intently.

“That, of course, applies to the Galarc Kingdom too. They will be trying to gain the most political benefit possible from Satsuki. Having said that, I’m sure you can imagine the potential dangers of the three of you suddenly appearing before Satsuki, right? The kingdom may try to take the three of you in as insurance, under the name of protection.”

“Uh...” Aki and Masato both gulped.

“I phrased it in a frightening way, but of course taking actions to upset Satsuki would normally be a poor move, so I doubt they’d try to pull anything so forceful,” Rio said with a bitter smile, shrugging his shoulders.

“That’s why I’m not saying you shouldn’t go meet Satsuki. But if you do go, I want you to be prepared. Just like Masato said, it’s very possible that you may not be able to return to this village so easily afterwards,” he continued.

“...Okay,” Miharu and the others nodded solemnly.

“And that’s all when it comes to the warnings I have to give. Of course, I’m willing to give my advice and present all the risks I can think of, but you all will make the final decision. I want to respect your opinions, which is why the three of you should think about it yourselves. And so I suggest we leave it at this for today,” Rio said, wrapping up the meeting for the day.

◇　◇　◇

After that, the group decided to head home right away in order to give Miharu, Aki, and Masato time to think. A rather heavy air hung over them on the road home — over the Japanese visitors in particular, who barely said a word. Sara, Orphia, and Alma read the mood and decided to watch over them silently for now. Meanwhile, Latifa was similarly staying silent out of consideration, but her gaze was fixed on Rio rather than Miharu. She walked beside him quietly while holding his hand, occasionally looking up at Rio’s face with a gentle look on her face.

Thus, the party arrived home.

“Since Rio’s returned today, I’ll do my best to make something nice for lunch,” Orphia said with the brightest voice she could after entering the house.

“I’ll help,” Rio immediately offered.

“Ah, me too...!” Miharu chimed in, lured along by Rio to reflexively offer to help.

“No, Rio should relax in the living room, please. And Miharu, don’t you have a lot to think about today? Leave this to me.” Orphia shook her head with a cheerful grin.

“...Okay, then, if you insist.” Rio nodded with a smile.

“Thank you, Orphia,” Miharu said apologetically.

“My cooking skills aren’t as good, but I’ll help instead, Orphia.”

“I can assist too.”

Sara and Alma both took the initiative to help out.

“Yup, the three of us can make something together for once!” Orphia agreed happily.

“...Orphia, should I help too?” Latifa offered hesitantly.

“Fufu, you should go and be spoiled by Rio while you still have a chance,” Orphia said with a smile. Latifa nodded with a soft smile of her own.

“Okay, thank you!”

Everyone went about their own business. Orphia, Sara, and Alma headed to the kitchen, while Rio and Latifa went to the living room and sat down on the sofa. Miharu, Aki, and Masato each retired to their own bedrooms.

Latifa seemed to be reading the mood in her own way, as she wasn’t enthusiastically pleading for Rio’s attention as usual, instead sticking close to Rio’s side quietly. She must have felt completely at ease there, as Latifa fell into a peaceful sleep within ten minutes or so, her head in Rio’s lap as she breathed gently in her sleep.

“Zzz... zzz...”

“...” The corners of Rio’s mouth relaxed faintly as he watched Latifa’s peacefully sleeping face while gently patting her head.

Suddenly, Miharu appeared in the living room, and approached Rio nervously. Despite having noticed Miharu’s approach, Rio continued to pet Latifa silently.

Miharu found her resolve and called out to Rio. “Umm, Haruto, do you have a moment?”

“...Yes, of course.” Rio smiled a little fleetingly and slowly nodded his head.

◇　◇　◇

Rio shifted the sleeping Latifa to rest on the sofa before following Miharu outside the house, at her request to be alone.

Rio stopped a slight distance away from Miharu and spoke up first. “What did you want to talk about?”

“...Umm, I wanted to know what you were thinking about all this,” Miharu began hesitantly.

“What I think?” Rio’s eyes widened slightly as he cocked his head to the side.

“Yes. What do you think we should be doing about this? I want to hear your opinion,” Miharu explained, clinging to Rio’s response.

“...Let’s see. I would attend the banquet alone and make contact with Satsuki. After hearing what Satsuki herself wants to do about all this, I’ll explore long-term solutions for what to do. Then, at possibly the same time, I’ll temporarily sneak Satsuki out of the castle and bring her to you guys, perhaps. Of course, I’ll have to have you three wait somewhere near the castle.” Rio offered what he considered to be the safest option.

“...That means you think we should meet Satsuki, right?” Miharu confirmed slowly.

“Yes. You would want to confirm each other’s safety with your own eyes first, right?” Rio asked.

“Yes,” Miharu nodded firmly in response.

“That would be the purpose of temporarily sneaking her out for a secret meeting. There’d be a fairly high risk in that alone, so it’s not an option that could be repeated often, but for a one time event there should be plenty of ways to make it happen,” Rio explained.

“If we wanted to keep seeing her we’d have to head to the castle ourselves, is what you mean?”

“If Satsuki is in a position where she can’t walk outside freely, that may be the only choice. Even if she could go out, someone would be keeping an eye on her friendships, so your existence would be revealed to the kingdom for sure,” Rio agreed with Miharu’s question with a contemplative look. What was more important was whether Miharu actually wanted to meet with Satsuki regardless of that.

“Then if — if the kingdom finds out about us, can we still remain with you even in that situation?” Miharu asked with an extremely worried face.

Rio hesitated slightly for a moment, before averting his eyes from the guilty-looking Miharu and answering. “I... wonder. If your existence were a weak point for Satsuki, I believe the kingdom would try to secure you and the siblings. Of course, that would depend on how much influence Satsuki has over the kingdom...”

There was a need to investigate in advance how the kingdom would treat Miharu, Aki, and Masato if they found out about them. Rio figured he’d be able to find out some of the specifics by contacting Satsuki on the night of the banquet. However, ultimately there was no way of knowing exactly what would happen until the moment unfurled.

At the very least, Rio currently had Liselotte of the Galarc Kingdom as a connection, which meant that relying on her assistance could be another option.

“Oh, right,” Miharu nodded, her shoulders slumping in disappointment.

“...However, if the three of you plan on returning to Japan one day, it would be ideal if you were to meet up with Takahisa as well. There’s no need to rush, but there’s no need to hold back from seeking assistance either, so please discuss it with Aki and Masato. Like I said earlier, you guys should be the ones to make the decision,” Rio said and smiled rather awkwardly.

Us... returning to Japan...

It was why the three were being protected by Rio. It was what they had discussed when they’d first arrived in this world and spoken to Rio.

However, the moment Miharu heard those words from Rio’s mouth once more, an indescribable sense of anxiety and panic rose within her, making her shrink in on herself. If Haruto was in fact the Haruto she’d once known, then would he have advised that they return to Japan? The thought overwhelmed her.

“U-Umm!” Before she knew it, Miharu’s mouth was moving.

“Yes?” Seeing the normally docile Miharu suddenly raise her voice in a rough manner made Rio’s eyes round in response.

“Do you — do you ever think about returning to Japan yourself, Haruto?” Miharu asked, looking extremely frustrated. She had avoided touching upon this delicate topic until now, but she simply had to know.

Rio hesitated for a moment before answering with a small sigh. “...That would be impossible.” He did not clearly specify whether he wanted to return or not.

“Why is that?” Miharu asked in a daze.

“Even if I were to return, the person I was in my previous life is already dead. If I were to return to Japan now, I would have no place to go. I wouldn’t even be on any kind of official record, you know?” Hints of a self-deprecating smile could be seen on Rio’s face as he answered with much difficulty.

“...But, don’t you have... I don’t know, regrets, or things you wished you had done?” Miharu asked. It was an intrusive question that was rare coming from her.

“...I wonder,” Rio replied, avoiding answering.

“Then, the Haruto of your previous life is...” Miharu tried to ask something, stumbling over her words, but Latifa’s voice suddenly echoed.

“Onii-chan?”

“What’s wrong, Latifa?” Rio said, looking in the direction the voice came from. At some point, the door to the house had opened, revealing Latifa standing there.

“Oh, it’s just that Onii-chan wasn’t there when I woke up, so...” Latifa said hesitantly.

“I see. Sorry, I was talking with Miharu,” Rio informed her, a gentle smile pasted on his face.

Latifa shook her head and approached Rio. “It’s okay. Are you done talking?”

“...Are we?” Rio asked Miharu.

“Ah, umm... Yes.” Miharu looked like she wanted to say something, but agreed indecisively instead.

“Then, I’m going for a short walk. I’d like to greet our neighbors now that I’ve returned, too. Orphia and the others seem to be making lunch, so I’ll be back soon. What would you like to do, Latifa?” Rio asked Latifa, distancing himself from Miharu.

Latifa paused for a moment, but slowly shook her head in the end. “...I’ll pass, it’s fine.”

“I see... Then I’ll be right back. Thanks, Latifa,” Rio said as he departed, patting Latifa on the shoulders.

“Yup, see you soon.” Latifa trembled with a flinch, nodding awkwardly as she saw Rio off.

So he noticed after all...

Latifa had been listening to Rio and Miharu’s conversation from the doorway from the middle of their talk — the reason why he thanked her was because of that. Latifa herself hadn’t even realized she’d timed her interruption as such, and felt an indescribable discomfort over that.

“...See you later, Haruto.” Miharu still looked like she wanted to say something, but swallowed her words as she saw Rio off.

◇　◇　◇

After Rio left, Latifa and Miharu were left alone by the doorway.

Miharu suddenly opened her mouth. “...Say, Latifa.”

“Hm? Yeah?” Latifa replied awkwardly.

“Umm, do you...” While Miharu had been the one to start talking, she seemed extremely unsure of her words. Her inner conflict was quite visible. “Latifa, how much do you know about Haruto?” she asked fearfully.

At present, the only ones who knew that Rio had memories of a previous life were the council of elders and Dryas herself. Sara, Orphia, Alma, and Latifa had been showing Miharu around, so they weren’t present and didn’t know. Rio told Miharu that himself, so Miharu had avoided talking about Rio’s previous life in front of the spirit folk girls until now.

However...

Miharu had a suspicion that Rio’s adopted sister might know about his past life.

“...What do you mean, how much?” Latifa asked hesitantly.

“I was just wondering if you knew why he uses the alias ‘Haruto,’ or something like that, maybe.” Miharu avoided Latifa’s eyes and spoke falteringly.

Latifa paused for a long moment before cutting to the point that Miharu had been trying to describe long-windedly. “...Are you perhaps asking about Onii-chan’s previous life?”

“S-So you do know about it after all.” Miharu’s expression suddenly changed, and she bit her lip.

“Yup, Onii-chan told me as proof of our sibling bond,” Latifa nodded.

“Then... Then... do you know, Latifa? If Haruto’s — Haruto’s alias... Was that his name in his previous life?” Miharu asked in earnest.

“...I can’t tell you that. Onii-chan asked me not to tell anyone anything about his previous life.” Latifa shook her head slowly.

“He said that...”

Miharu wondered what exactly that could mean. It wasn’t something one would to want spread normally. She didn’t know why he didn’t want it spread, but she couldn’t accept it was just because of a matter of privacy.

That being said, she couldn’t force Latifa to tell her, so Miharu simply clenched her hands into fists.

“Even if you can’t ask me, why don’t you just ask Onii-chan yourself?” Latifa suggested with a very troubled look.

“...It might just be my imagination, but it feels like he’s avoiding me. Especially ever since he came back this time,” Miharu said, frowning sadly.

I kinda thought the same thing. But I also thought it was just my imagination...

Rio really did seem like he was avoiding Miharu earlier, Latifa thought. She first noticed something was odd during the exchange between Rio returning to the village and before they entered the town hall together. It was as though Rio was purposefully avoiding Miharu’s eyes...

But even if that were true, then Miharu was behaving strangely, too. Ever since Rio returned, her eyes and attention had continuously been focused on him.

“...Why do you want to know about Onii-chan’s past life?” Latifa asked, examining Miharu’s expression.

“If I answer that, will you tell me Haruto’s name in his previous life?” Miharu seemed extremely frustrated as she brought up a way for them to swap information.

“I can’t do that.” Latifa shook her head slowly.

“...Sorry, that was unfair of me to say. I’m sorry,” Miharu apologized shamefully. It was behavior she would have never shown under normal circumstances, so she must have felt exceptionally defeated.

“No, it’s okay...” Latifa said with a contemplative look, searching Miharu’s face for her feelings.

Maybe... no, it’s more likely that Miharu...

Based on their exchange up until now, Latifa was practically certain that Miharu suspected Rio was Amakawa Haruto in his previous life.

But... from when?

When had she realized it? Because their names were the same? If that was the only factor, she would have taken some kind of action long ago. There must have been some other factor, Latifa thought.

Ah, was it then...? Latifa suddenly thought of something and understood.

It was back when they had made the apple cake during cooking class — they were talking about the first time Rio and Latifa came to the village. As they described how Rio was thrown into a jail cell, Orphia and Alma said they had heard Rio mutter ‘Mii-chan’ in his sleep.

Back then, Latifa noticed that Miharu’s expression had clearly changed. She hadn’t acted strangely after that, but it was possible that she’d started holding onto her suspicions then. Then, after actually seeing Rio again, that doubt grew stronger.

Has Onii-chan noticed Miharu’s change in behavior? Is that why he’s avoiding her? Latifa suspected.

“Latifa?” Miharu tilted her head awkwardly, peering at Latifa’s face. Latifa had been lost in her own thoughts, so Miharu was most likely wondering what was going on with her.

Latifa thought hard for a moment before slowly moving her mouth. “...Say, Miharu.”

“What is it?”

“I can’t tell you about Onii-chan’s previous life. But I can tell you about my past life,” Latifa stated, having made up her mind.

“Eh...?” Miharu was dumbfounded. For a moment, she didn’t understand what Latifa had said, as she had no idea that Latifa had a past life.

“I have a past life too. A story I’ve only told Onii-chan. But I’ll tell it to you too, because it’s you. My conditions are that you stay silent about what I say, and that you answer one of my questions after I’m done,” Latifa said with determination and looked directly at Miharu.

“Latifa...” Miharu was baffled by the sudden topic at hand.

“Well? Do you accept these terms? Though it isn’t fair to just say that when you know nothing about my past life, so I’ll tell you one thing up front. I knew Onii-chan in my past life. We died in the same traffic accident.”

“Ah...” Miharu gasped in shock.

“I might change my mind later, so I’m only going to wait ten seconds. Ten, nine, eight...”

“W-Wait! I want to hear it. Please tell me, Latifa. I promise to abide by your conditions.”

“Got it. Sorry, this time I was the one saying unfair things. But in exchange, I’ll tell you about my past life. I don’t think you’ll regret it,” Latifa said apologetically.

She wanted to know Miharu’s feelings. Just like how Miharu wanted to know about Rio’s past life, Latifa wanted to know why Miharu was digging into Rio’s past life.

Miharu shook her head politely, “It’s okay. I don’t want to be pushy, but will you tell me right away?”

“Yup. I was an elementary school student in my past life. Onii-chan was a university student, and we knew each other because we took the same bus to our schools.”

“...” Miharu was focused on listening, so she didn’t say a word.

“At first, I wasn’t used to riding the bus. I only used it occasionally on rainy days, but I once missed my stop and went somewhere I was unfamiliar with. When I got scared and started crying, Onii-chan brought me back home. That was my first meeting with Onii-chan. That was all it took for me to... No, the Onii-chan of my past life was so kind and handsome, I fell in love with him at first sight. Then I made mom let me take the bus to school. And that was one year before we died...”

Latifa paused there before continuing, fondly remembering the details.

“But in the end, even with one year’s worth of time, I never gained the courage to talk to Onii-chan ever again. Ah, I know I asked why you couldn’t talk to Onii-chan yourself before, but now that I think about it, I’m really not one to talk about Miharu, huh? I still have lots of things I haven’t had the courage to say, even now.” Latifa smiled sadly.

“Latifa...” Miharu clenched her fists tightly from the heartache.

“That’s why I wasn’t actually that close to Onii-chan in my previous life. Of course, since becoming the me of this world, I’ve heard lots of stories from Onii-chan, but I promised him I wouldn’t tell anyone about that. Sorry — I couldn’t tell you much, I guess?” Latifa apologized regretfully. Perhaps she had just wanted to tell someone about herself. Maybe she wanted Miharu to know about her — it was, perhaps, why she brought up such a topic.

“That’s not true.” Miharu smiled fleetingly, shaking her head.

“Thank you. Then, to finish things off, I’ll tell you a little about what kind of person Onii-chan looked like to my previous self. And to my current self too...” After saying that, a certain intention could be glimpsed in Latifa’s eyes. It was possible that talking about her impression of Haruto from when she was Suzune would be a violation of the promise she made Rio. At the very least, it was definitely a grey area.

But Latifa wanted to say it anyway. She had to say it, she thought. If she was to remain in love with Rio in the future, she thought she had to face Miharu directly right here and now. “Onii-chan always... The Onii-chan in my memory always had a sad look on his face. He had a faraway look in his eyes, as though he was watching someone who wasn’t there. Like someone very important was gone, and he knew they wouldn’t be returning...”

Latifa knew who that important person was. She was already treading on a dangerous line at this point, so she couldn’t say any further than that.

“Haruto was...” Miharu blinked.

“I don’t know... I don’t know if Onii-chan is still looking at that person even now. But, you know. I love Onii-chan. He saved me in this world as well.”

“R-Really?” Latifa’s sudden confession had Miharu recoiling her head.

“Yup. Come to think of it, I’ve never told you about what happened... About the life I was living before I came to the village...”

“I heard you were traveling with Haruto...” Miharu said nervously.

“It was before that. I-I was... I was a slave before. By the time I regained my memories of my past life in this world, I had been born and raised as a slave.”

“You’re just digging your own grave...” Despite Aki’s exasperation, she couldn’t hold back her giggles.

“S-Shut up!” Masato yelled in a fluster.

“Well, whatever. What will you do, then? Do you want to stay at the village and continue your sword training?” Aki asked Masato, trying to recover their derailed conversation.

Masato scratched his head shyly. “Ah, well. If it’s come to this, I’ll have to bow my head to Haruto too. I want to go to Strahl as well.”

“Hmm, so you’re coming after all. You didn’t seem that enthusiastic about it...” Aki stared closely at Masato’s face.

“Shut up. I changed my mind.” Masato turned away.

“Oh, really.” A smile tugged at Aki’s lips.

“Fufu.” Miharu watched the two of them with an amused smile on her face. They finally felt like their usual selves again. But with that decided, they had to make haste.

“First, let’s all go to Haruto. Then we’ll call Sara and the girls over and give our report together,” Miharu suggested.

“Yup.”

“Okay.”

Aki and Masato nodded in unison.

With that decided, the three of them visited Rio’s room and knocked on the door, with Rio’s reply coming immediately. “Come in.”

“Wait, Latifa?!” It seemed there was something of a commotion inside.

“Excuse me...” Miharu opened the door fearfully. Rio was carrying Latifa on his back — or rather, Latifa was clinging to Rio’s back. “Good evening, Miharu.”

“Umm, good evening, Haruto. Do you have a moment right now?” Seeing Rio carrying Latifa on his back made Miharu hesitate.

Rio smiled faintly “Yes, we were just messing around. If the three of you are here together, it means you’ve come to a decision, right?”

“Yes,” Miharu said.

“Ahaha, you’re so attached to Haruto, Latifa.” When Aki spotted Latifa clinging to Rio’s back, she couldn’t help but give a slightly strained smile at the display of affection between the two.

“Yup!” Latifa nodded with a carefree smile.

“For now, please come inside. Latifa, can you go to the living room or back to your own room?”

“Eeh, but I wanna hear too.” Latifa pouted.

“It’s an important conversation. You understand that, right?” Rio warned her with a troubled look. At that, Latifa puffed up her cheeks and climbed off his back, obediently moving to leave the room.

“Umm, Latifa can stay,” Miharu said. “Actually, we were thinking of calling Sara and the others over too, so that we could all talk together. About our thoughts.”

“With me too?” Latifa cocked her head hesitantly.

“Yup. I want you to listen too,” Miharu said, smiling gently.

“I understand. Let’s talk in the living room, then.” Rio respected their decision and suggested they relocate.

◇　◇　◇

Sara, Orphia, and Alma were called to Rio’s living room. Once everyone had gathered and taken their seats on the sofa, Rio spoke up.

“Now, could you tell us what the three of you have decided to do?”

Miharu took a deep breath. “Yes. Firstly, the three of us have reached the conclusion that we all want to go to Strahl.”

“I understand. If that’s first, then is there more?” Rio asked.

That request was well within his expectations. There was nothing to be surprised about. Neither Latifa nor the spirit folk girls seemed particularly shocked, either. However —

“I would... I would like to attend the night banquet with you.” Latifa and the spirit folk girls twitched in reaction.

“...If the kingdom finds out about you, the royalty and nobility may try to find a way to use you. I’m sure they will treat you politely on the surface, but that would mean revealing your name and face to the public from here onwards. It’s possible that people who will try to use that for their own plots may appear. You are aware of all this, yet still want to attend the banquet. Is that correct?” Miharu’s request to attend the banquet too had been a little unexpected, making Rio pause for a moment before confirming her intentions.

“...Yes,” Miharu nodded deeply, conveying her own determination. Even if she couldn’t attend the banquet, if she made herself available to meet Satsuki at any moment, she would be well-known at some point. It was just a matter of whether it was sooner or later.

But more than anything, Miharu hated leaving everything to Rio alone. While leaving everything to Rio might certainly be a wise choice, it also felt like Rio would go somewhere far away, which made her feel quite scared. This choice was Miharu’s own selfish desire — it was her chance to take her future into her own hands. Now, whether Rio would accept her selfishness or not was another thing.

Miharu watched Rio’s face closely, feeling a little scared.

“...Then, let me confirm one more thing. If this is for you, then what about Aki and Masato?” Rio asked, looking at them.

Miharu wrung out all her courage to answer Rio’s question. “I was hoping they could wait near the castle.”

“...Depending on how our discussion goes, it’s possible that Aki and Masato won’t be able to meet Satsuki even if they go to Strahl. You might be going for no reason, you realize?” Rio asked.

“Yes, we have taken that into account. After the three of us talked, I made this request of them. This is what we decided,” Miharu said resolutely.

“I see...” Rio gave a small sigh and looked at Aki and Masato once more. The two of them nodded and returned his gaze. They didn’t look like they had anything further to say; Rio could tell that they had truly accepted this.

Meanwhile, the spirit folk girls were all watching them silently.

“Is that okay, Haruto? Or is taking the three of us too difficult...” Masato asked fearfully and bowed his head toward Rio. Though Rio could use spirit arts to fly, there was no way he could carry Miharu, Aki, and Masato together while doing so.

“I have to make sure I fly safely, of course, but that doesn’t mean its impossible,” Rio replied to Masato with a wry smile. On the other hand, Sara, Orphia, and Alma all exchanged secret glances.

“Then...” Masato and Aki gulped, awaiting Rio’s conclusion.

“If that is the answer the three of you have arrived at after careful consideration, then we shall proceed with that.” Rio smiled gently. If this decision of theirs had been made lightly, he would have given them more warning, but he could tell that wasn’t the case.

“Yay!” Masato and Aki said together, high-fiving each other.

“That’s great.” Sara smiled with the other girls, watching Masato and Aki.

“...Are you sure?” Miharu had been expecting more resistance, so when everything went so smoothly, her eyes widened in surprise.

“Yes. You are the one who asked, no?” Rio said with an amused look.

“Umm, but, I thought you would oppose us going to the castle. It’ll be an inconvenience to you too, so... umm...”

“That’s not true. Like I said — I’ll respect your decisions. If it’s to help the three of you return to Japan one day, then I’ll exert every effort to help. All the more so if this is an answer you considered carefully. That’s why, instead of worrying about being a nuisance or burden to me, I’d like you to push thoughts like that out of your mind,” Rio said calmly to a frowning Miharu.

“...Okay.” When Rio had said ‘return to Japan,’ Miharu couldn’t help but feel vexed and saddened, her face distorting faintly. However, she immediately corrected it into a serious face and agreed slowly.

Latifa seemed to sense something, watching Miharu with a frustrated look herself.

“However, there will of course be precautions we must take in order to allow Miharu to attend the banquet, so I expect you to follow those. Is that okay?” Rio stared fixedly at Miharu, emphasizing his words.

“Y-Yes. Thank you for your consideration.” Miharu nodded deeply and bowed her head to Rio.

“As you can see, I am disguised when in front of other people, but... It’s kind of embarrassing being stared at like that?” Celia said, shyly tilting her head and seeking Rio for help. However, Rio just chuckled and shrugged.

“Wait, huh? Don’t tell me... is there something weird about me?” Celia gasped, searching her hair and face in a panic; she was feeling to see if her appearance had fallen out of sorts in a flustered manner. However, when she couldn’t find any abnormality, she watched Rio’s expression beside her as she hesitantly lowered her hands.

“Everyone’s surprised at how cute you are, Professor,” Rio offered with an amused look.

“C-Cute... W-Why are you smiling?” Celia blushed and puffed up her cheeks, glaring at Rio reproachfully.

“I’m sorry. I didn’t think everyone would be this nervous, so it was funny to me,” Rio said with a huff of laughter at Miharu and the other girls.

“...Excuse me,” Sara bowed. “You’re just so beautiful, I couldn’t help but stare in awe.”

“T-Thank you.” Celia thanked her in embarrassment at the frank praise.

“Next, I’ll introduce Sara and the others,” Rio continued. “There’s a few of them, so any detailed talk can be saved for later between yourselves.”

“Okay,” Sara said.

“This is Sara. She’s the same age as me and we met after I first ran away from Beltrum. We’ve had a close relationship ever since, but she’s actually not a human from the Strahl region.”

“She’s one of the people you were talking about before, right? Of the people you met who lived secretly in the Wilderness...” Celia observed the expressions on Rio and the girls and confirmed fearfully.

“Yes, they’re the ones who live there,” Rio said. He had kept information about the spirit folk village secret until now, but he had obtained Sara’s acceptance to reveal it now that everything had come to this.

“I see...” Celia looked at their faces once more. Their existence had come up in conversation briefly before, so she did have a small hunch about it, but she’d never expected to actually meet the people living outside of the Strahl region.

“They’re officially called ‘spirit folk,’ but it’s only an umbrella term, so it doesn’t refer to their specific species. That’s where their secret lies, you can say...” Realizing the need to explain further, Rio grasped for words as he glanced over at them.

“Rio, I’ll take over from here,” Sara said as she took a small deep breath, feeling it best if she revealed the secret herself.

“Sure, please go ahead.” Rio nodded deeply.

“...Just like how you trusted Rio and us enough to reveal your identity, we also trust you as Rio’s teacher, and will reveal our own identities.” Sara, speaking somewhat in an uneasy manner, nervously took off the necklace she had been wearing. Up until now, Sara only appeared as though she was human. However, wolf ears popped out of her head as she took off the necklace. At the same time, a fluffy tail also came into view.

“Huh?!” Celia widened her eyes in shock.

“The magic artifact Sara just took off holds disguising sorcery more complex than in the one used to change your hair color, Professor. You can clearly see why it was used,” Rio explained from the side.

In the Strahl region, werebeasts, dwarves, and elves were species that couldn’t exist as normal citizens — the only exception were slaves like Latifa had been. On top of that, their population was extremely small. Thus, their value as a commodity was high, and many royals and wealthy merchants craved to own them as pet slaves.

Because of this, Sara and the others were afraid because they couldn’t imagine how Celia would think of them. Rio had told them that it would be fine in advance, but they still couldn’t ease their anxieties.

“Oh, umm, are you a were... beast?” Celia blinked her eyes intensely and stared at Sara’s face and ears. She was simply surprised, with no sign of greed or disdain in her eyes.

“Yes, this is Sara, a silver werewolf-type of werebeast,” Rio replied.

“Nice to meet you,” Sara bowed her head timidly.

“Yes, you too...” Celia meekly bowed her head back.

“Umm, what do you think about me?” Sara, taking a plunge, asked straightforwardly.

“Well, it’s my first time seeing such a thing, so I’m simply surprised, I guess. You’re really cute,” a puzzled Celia answered.

“...Thank you,” Sara replied with a bewildered expression. Orphia, Alma, and Latifa breathed a sigh of relief, reassured by Celia’s reaction.

“It’s just as I said, right? That Professor Celia would interact with all of you like normal people,” Rio said to them and chuckled.

“What do you mean?” Celia asked in confusion.

“You know how non-human species get treated like slaves in the Strahl region?”

“Oh, I get it now. Of course you’d be wary because of that. I’m sorry,” Celia said a strained smile.

“N-No, you don’t need to apologize! If anything, we’re sorry for antagonizing you without any basis,” Sara apologized back in a fluster.

“It’s all right — don’t worry about it,” Celia said with a smile, and looked at Orphia, Alma, and Latifa who were all sitting together. “But if you’re a werebeast, then are the other three over there also...?”

“I’m a high elf, and my name is Orphia!” Orphia exclaimed, introducing herself with a smile. Then, like Sara, she took off her artifact necklace and revealed her elf ears.

“I’m Alma, an elder dwarf.” Alma bowed before she also took off her necklace. Once she did, her narrow dwarf ears came into view.

With puzzled eyes at the appearances of the two new species, Celia turned to Rio next to her. “...I remember reading about this before, but high elves and elder dwarves are like the royalty of elves and dwarves, right?”

“Yes. Monarchy doesn’t actually exist in their village, but viewing it in that way might make it easier to understand. Sara also comes from a prestigious family in her village, so all three of them are the princesses in their respective species.”

“Oh, I see... Who’s the other one, then?”

And why are you traveling with people of such high status? — thought Celia, but she turned to stare at Latifa, who sat quietly next to Sara.

“I’m a werefox, and my name is Latifa! I’m Onii-chan’s little sister! Nice to meet you!” Latifa awkwardly introduced herself with a high-pitched voice, her whole body tensed up. After hurriedly taking off her necklace like the others, her fox ears and tail appeared.

“...Yeah, nice meeting you. Wait, s-sister?! You had a sister?! And such an adorable one with fox ears at that! Y-You never told me!” Celia gazed at Latifa’s fox ears with an astounded face as she bowed, but once she processed Latifa’s words in her mind, her expression changed at once and she turned on Rio.

“P-Professor, please calm down. I’ll explain everything,” Rio said in a fluster, but then, Aishia returned from the kitchen.

“The tea has been brewed. Let it steam for a few more minutes and it’ll be ready to drink.” After placing the tray with the tea on the table, she sat in the empty spot next to Rio.

“Y-Yeah...” Celia calmed at Aishia’s appearance, feeling embarrassed when she realized how she had lost her cool in front of the others.

“There’s too much to explain, so I’ll just give you the overview for now. I met Latifa after I ran away from the Kingdom of Beltrum. I ended up taking care of her, so although we’re not connected by blood, I became her guardian as an older brother,” Rio explained concisely.

“Oh, I see...” Celia nodded dejectedly. There were still many things she wanted to ask, but she refrained from derailing the conversation.

“And so, Latifa, Miharu, Aki, and Masato have been living hidden in Sara’s village until now, but with the discovery of the hero Satsuki’s whereabouts, I’m bringing them back to the Strahl region. It would be difficult to transport them all to the Strahl region by myself, so Sara and the others helped carry them. They’re also using this opportunity to deepen their insights outside their village,” Rio explained, getting straight to the point.

“...I get the overall gist. So you’re talking about the three over there, right?” Letting a small breath out, Celia glanced over at the group sitting away from Sara.

“Yes. They were the three involved in the summoning of the heroes. The oldest girl is Miharu, the other girl is Aki, and the boy is Aki’s younger brother, Masato,” Rio said, introducing them all together.

“Hi, I’m Miharu Ayase. Nice to meet you,” Miharu greeted a bit nervously.

“I’m Aki Sendo.”

“I’m Masato Sendo.”

“Pleased to meet you too. Miharu, Aki, Masato, right? And then Sara, Orphia, Alma, Latifa... Okay, I’ve memorized everyone’s names. Once again, nice to meet you all. Oh, do you mind if I speak to you informally? You can call me anything you want in the house as well,” Celia replied with a soft smile.

“Of course,” everyone agreed at the same time.

“But wow, I’m amazed. Even though there’s so many people...” Masato said in awe at Celia’s quick memorization of everyone’s names and faces.

“Her mind works differently from yours,” Aki said with a giggle.

“Heh, and yours too, Aki. She’s pretty and has a nice personality — how perfect,” Masato retaliated with a smirk.

“S-Shut up. I knew that from the moment I saw her,” Aki pouted in indignation.

“Haha, the siblings are fighting again. You’re so close, aren’t you?” Latifa smiled in amusement.

“That’s not true!” Aki and Masato denied in unison.

“...Fufu, how funny,” Celia’s eyes widened as she smiled softly.

Rio observed Celia’s facial expression and decided to announce the start of their new living arrangements. “So, I’m sorry about how sudden this is, but until the aforementioned banquet starts, everyone will be living here together for a while. It might get a little rowdy...”

“Of course, I’m all for it. It’s only been me and Aishia for a while, so I’m looking forward to things getting livelier around here,” Celia said happily with a laugh. Although there were still many complicated issues at the forefront, she somehow felt as though exciting days were about to begin.

◇　◇　◇

They talked in the living room for nearly an hour after that. However, with the time being evening, Masato’s growling stomach signaled the start of dinner preparations.

“We’ll prepare dinner tonight, so Rio should go take a bath with Masato,” suggested Orphia, and so it was decided that Rio and Masato would bathe together first. After Rio and Masato headed to the bath, washed their bodies, and relaxed in the bathtub —

“...Hey, Haruto,” Masato suddenly said.

“Hm? What’s up?” Rio was absentmindedly staring up at the ceiling, but turned his gaze to Masato. Then, because Masato had an unexpectedly serious look on his face, he found himself reflexively adjusting his posture.

“Do you like anyone within the group, Haruto?” Masato asked abruptly.

“...You scared me for a moment there. What’s up with this, all of a sudden?” The anticlimax had Rio deflating, hanging his head tiredly.

“Well, I was just wondering if you never felt anything, being surrounded by such impressive girls.” Masato laughed out loud before explaining his thought process behind the question.

“I mean, I don’t know what to say...” Rio looked up at the ceiling with a worried face.

“And? Who is it?” Masato asked insistently.

“This isn’t the time for that, I think,” Rio replied, a faint smile on his face.

“Why?” Masato asked curiously.

“...Because I was originally traveling with a purpose. Even if I liked someone, I wouldn’t be able to stay with them forever. That’s why it’s not the time to be falling for anyone,” Rio said a little sadly.

“That’s... not true, though? You can just travel together.” Masato tilted his head in doubt.

“It’s not as simple as that, probably...” Rio smiled bitterly. Having crossed swords with Lucius and making him aware of his existence, Rio could no longer turn back. From here on, it was an exchange of blood for blood. Rio would try to kill Lucius, and Lucius would reciprocate.

As long as either of them survived... No, even if one of them succeeded, a new grudge could be born in someone else instead. It would be the start of a vicious cycle of revenge. He would have to live in fear of an invisible danger — of being sought as a target of revenge himself. That was what it meant to devote yourself to revenge.

And so, he couldn’t seek his own happiness, couldn’t expose the person he liked to danger over someone as worthless as himself — that was what Rio thought, though he didn’t voice it out loud. Instead —

“What about you, Masato? Is there a girl in the house that you like?” he asked Masato, hoping to distract him.

“Nope, there isn’t.” Masato shook his head bluntly.

“How come?” asked Rio.

“No, well... I guess I did ask you a similar question.” Masato hummed in thought and scratched his head. “I mean, I think everyone’s pretty cute. I admire them too. Honestly, they’re all beautiful. But...”

“But?” Rio parroted back at Masato.

“It’s just, I don’t really see them in that way for some reason. I guess I’ve been around them for so long, they all seem like my older sisters. And...” Masato trailed off, staring at Rio.

Aki aside, it seems like all the others are in love with you already. I’ve only just met Celia, and I get the same feeling from her too. Ah, but I’m not too sure about Miharu...

“...And, what?” Rio stared back at Masato curiously.

“No, it’s nothing. I might get out now. I’m getting lightheaded.” Masato shook his head with a wry smile and stood up.

“...It looks like you’ve been training properly.” Rio observed Masato’s muscles from close up and grinned.

“...Wait, is it possible that you like men, Haruto?!” Masato gasped and hurried to hide his body.

“Give me a break,” Rio denied in exasperation.

◇　◇　◇

Meanwhile, during the time Rio and Masato were in the bath, the entire group of eight girls — Miharu, Aishia, Celia, Latifa, Sara, Orphia, Alma, and Aki — were working together to prepare dinner. Miharu and Orphia took the lead in the cooking and the other girls assisted them, progressing smoothly but noisily.

Eventually, Rio and Masato left the bathroom, and within an hour, dinner was ready. The dining table Dominic had set up boasted a fairly large size, but with ten peoples’ worth of food, it was packed rather tightly.

“I want to be next to Onii-chan! Celia can sit over there!” Latifa swiftly and shrewdly acquired her seat next to Rio, then urged Celia into the seat on Rio’s other side.

“Thank you... Then, if you don’t mind,” Celia giggled and took the seat next to Rio. Aishia sat beside her. Miharu, Sara, and the others also took their seats. Then once everyone was seated at the dining table —

“Let’s eat!” Orphia declared, and they began their social dinner with the goal of getting to know Celia.

“Thank you for the food! It looks great again today. I’m so hungry! Yum!” Masato’s eyes sparkled as he reached for the delicious food with his chopsticks. He stuffed his cheeks with the piping hot karaage, puffing as he gave his thoughts. He then proceeded to gulp down white rice.

“Mind your table manners — it’s embarrassing. Celia’s here too,” Aki puffed her cheeks and muttered.

“Fufu, I think boys look much cooler when they eat heartily,” Celia complimented Masato with a smile.

“Heh, hear that?!” Masato grinned happily.

“...Don’t let it get to your head.” Aki sighed tiredly.

“You should eat too, Aki. Miharu and the others went out of their way to make us such delicious food, after all.”

“Wha— hey, I helped too! I made some of it!”

“Heh, which one?” Masato asked with a smirk.

“Ugh... T-This salad and the dressing.” Aki blushed and pointed at the salad and dressing placed on the table.

“Hmm, I guess it looks good.”

“It tastes good too! I know you don’t like vegetables, but make sure you eat some,” Aki said, serving some onto Masato’s plate.

“I-I’m fine. Hey, not that much!” Masato tried to stop Aki in a panic, but it was too late. A heap of vegetables was placed on the plate before Masato.

“Blergh. I hate tomatoes...” Masato groaned in disappointment.

“You won’t grow as strong as Haruto if you’re picky about your food,” Aki said.

“This salad dressing is delicious, Aki. It’s been emulsified properly.” Rio must have been listening to their conversation, as he spoke up.

“T-Thank you very much.” The sudden words took Aki by surprise, and she thanked him shyly. The bustling meal continued for a while, when Celia suddenly spoke up, as though the thought suddenly came to mind.

“By the way, Rio. Have you decided on your plans for the future? There’s still some time before the banquet.”

“Yes, about that. Miharu wants to attend the banquet too, so I was thinking of going to Amande together to propose a meeting with Liselotte. There’s no guarantee we can see her right away, so it may take several days...”

“True, you won’t know that until you go. Then will we be waiting here?”

“Yes. I’ll plan for us to all go shopping some other time, if you don’t mind.”

“I understand. I’ll spend this time getting closer to everyone else,” Celia said contently, looking between Sara, Latifa, and the others.

“Ehehe, I’m looking forward to it!” Latifa smiled happily.

“I’m sure you’ll get along with everyone in no time at all, Professor. It seems like they’ve warmed up to you a lot already.” Rio looked around the dining table, smiling.

“Yes, they’ve already taught me some cooking, and we promised to all bathe together later. Right?” Celia said in a pleasant mood, looking at Latifa.

“Yes!” Latifa nodded energetically. Her speech was a little stiff towards Celia, but that was possibly because they had the biggest age gap out of everyone present. That being said, there was no distance to be felt between them, so there wasn’t a problem.

“Look after the Professor with everyone while I’m gone, Latifa.” Rio smiled gently as he spoke to Latifa.

“Yup!” Latifa said with a carefree smile.

“You two are close siblings in a way that’s different from Aki and Masato, aren’t you?” Celia smiled gently, looking at Aki and Masato, who would bicker with each other at every chance they got.

◇　◇　◇

After the dishes were put away and everyone caught their breaths, Rio offered to clean up.

“I’ll clean up the rest, so everyone can go relax.”

“Then as promised, let’s all go take that bath together!” Latifa suggested and up energetically.

“Fufu, then let’s get ready after we’re done with our tea. I’ll help clean up too.” Orphia took the initiative to agree and immediately offered to assist Rio in cleaning up. At practically the same time, Miharu stood up to help too.

“It’s fine, Orphia, Miharu. This is my thanks for making the delicious meal,” Rio said, directing the two of them to rest at ease.

“Then I’ll help carry the tableware, Haruto!” Masato said, offering to help out for once.

“Please do,” Rio said.

“Thank you, Onii-chan, Masato! I’m going to get ready then!” Latifa thanked the two of them before immediately heading to her room to prepare for the bath. Thus, as Rio and Masato cleaned up, the women left to undress together. They each returned to their room to get ready and head to the changing room.

“Ehehe, I’m first!” Latifa took off her clothes before anyone else and ran towards the bathtub.

“Latifa, don’t run inside here.” Sara was just in the middle of removing her bra when she spotted Latifa running inside. She placed a hand against her hip and called out to Latifa, causing her bra to softly fall to the ground.

“Fufu, how bold of you,” Orphia giggled at Sara.

“G-Geez, don’t stare at me. W-What is it, Celia?” Sara hurriedly hid her chest, but she noticed Celia staring at her and shrunk back in question.

“Nothing, it’s just... your tail...” Celia continued to stare at Sara’s tail.

“My... tail?” Sara tilted her head curiously.

Celia mustered her courage and pleaded: “Umm... M-May I please touch it?”

“...Sure, I don’t mind,” Sara agreed, smiling in amusement and agreed.

“Then, if you’d excuse me...”

“Go ahead.”

Celia reached her hand out timidly, while Sara picked up her own tail to make it easier to touch. When Celia’s hand gently reached Sara’s tail, her eyes widened in amazement.

“This is... such a thick coat!” It was bushy, but soft, making it a wonderful texture to the touch. Celia petted Sara’s tail, absorbed in how fluffy it was. Each time she touched the tail, Sara would shiver from the ticklish sensation.

“U-Umm, it feels nice, but it’s a little ticklish,” Sara said with a faint blush.

“Ah, I’m sorry! It just felt so nice to touch, I completely lost myself for a moment...” Celia laughed apologetically.

“N-No, please continue petting all you like,” Sara requested with a grin.

“Yes please! I’d even love to wash it!” Celia returned happily. Sara blinked blankly for a moment, before nodding with a giggle.

“...Okay. Then, if you would please.”

“Fufu, we’re going to go in first. Let’s go,” Orphia said in amusement as she, Miharu, Aki, and Alma passed them to enter the bath. Celia and Sara quickly followed them. Inside, Latifa and Aishia were already washing their bodies.

“Hmm, hm-hmm,” Latifa was humming a song as her tail swished from side to side rhythmically.

...I’d love to touch Latifa’s tail too. Celia stared at Latifa’s tail with great interest, deciding to ask to touch it later. For now, she had to wash her own body first.

“Now, shall we wash our hair and bodies too?” Celia suggested, lining up with Sara at the washing area and sitting on a stool. She began to carefully wash her hair, face, and body.

After Sara had carefully washed everywhere except her tail — “Umm, did you still want to wash my tail like you said?” she asked Celia beside her shyly.

“Yes, with pleasure! Is it okay to wash it just like with normal hair?” Celia said happily and moved her stool behind Sara.

“Yes, that would be fine.” Sara nodded.

“Then, I’m going to wash it now.” Celia gently grasped Sara’s tail and drenched it with warm water first, then used shampoo to gently create bubbles.

“Fufu, it feels good.” Sara smiled, feeling a little ticklish.

Chapter 7: To Amande Once More

The next afternoon, Rio departed from the rock house placed in the outskirts of the Galarc Kingdom to visit Amande. Miharu accompanied him, and Aishia was in her spirit form.

They were finally going to Liselotte’s mansion.

The two of them went to the gate at the northern area of the city and went through all the designated processes before going to the mansion.

“Are you nervous, Miharu?” Rio asked the stiff-faced girl as they walked.

“Yes, a little. This will be my first time meeting a noble...” Miharu nodded awkwardly. She had already met a noble daughter when it came to Celia, but it appeared she had forgotten that fact.

“Cecilia’s a noble too. Or does she not appear that way?” Rio informed her, using the alias that was decided. He was trying to ease Miharu’s nerves and had a teasing smile on his face.

“...Ah, umm, in Cecilia’s case, I heard in advance that she was close to you, so she didn’t seem that way, or something... Of course, I think she’s beautiful and intelligent, just like a princess, you know?” Miharu gasped and excused herself in a fluster. In reality, from Miharu’s point of view, Celia was wonderful and had quite a presence to behold.

“She would be delighted to hear that. If you’re not nervous interacting with Cecilia, then you should be fine with Liselotte too, so don’t be so tense,” Rio said, smiling naturally.

“Okay,” Miharu nodded, peeking at Rio’s side profile.

Thank goodness I can still speak normally even when I’m alone with Haruto. She sighed in relief.

It may have been Miharu’s imagination, but she was a little worried that recently it felt like her relationship with Rio had been a little awkward. In particular, after Rio had returned to the village to inform them of Satsuki’s whereabouts, and Miharu had tried to ask Rio about his previous life...

There were most likely two causes: the first was that Miharu herself was strongly convinced that Haruto — that Rio — was Amakawa Haruto. This one was for certain.

Then, as for the other... For some reason, ever since Rio had returned to the village, it felt like he had been distancing himself somewhat. Of course, he wouldn’t do that in an obvious way and acted normal when they were with everyone else, but Miharu could feel a distance that was hard to put to words. It was different to being pushed away, more like being avoided...

It made Miharu feel sad. That’s why she was a little anxious about today — she’d be in a situation with just the two of them. While part of her nerves was because of meeting Liselotte, the majority of it was because she had to be alone with Rio.

That being said, Aishia was with them too in her spirit form, so they technically weren’t alone. On top of that, Miharu herself knew that her thoughts should be focused on other things right now, so she kept her doubts hidden in her heart.

That’s right — today I’m here on behalf of Aki and Masato. This was my own selfish request, Miharu thought, refocusing her mind.

“For now, I’ll do all the talking, so you can just focus on listening to Liselotte and I converse. It’s enough if you just reply whenever Liselotte or I address you directly. A topic to be careful about would be if Liselotte brings up products appropriated from Earth knowledge.” Rio must have thought Miharu’s expression was of discomfort, as he spoke to her gently.

“O-Okay. I’ll do my best, just like we discussed before,” Miharu said with firm determination.

Liselotte Cretia. The fact she was appropriating knowledge from Earth to develop products in this world was basically an undeniable fact to Rio and the visitors from Earth. Consequently, they had deeply considered all the possible reactions Liselotte might show if Miharu, a Japanese person, showed up.

“You’ll be fine, Miharu. Aishia’s here in her spirit form too.”

“...Yeah. Please take care of me, Ai-chan,” Miharu giggled.

“I’m counting on you if the worst happens, Aishia,” Rio said. That being said, the actual chance of ‘the worst’ happening was very low. It was nothing more than Rio’s presumption, but having interacted with Liselotte several times now and seeing her interact with the hero Sakata Hiroaki in a normal manner, he was sure her attitude wouldn’t suddenly change.

Got it, Aishia replied curtly.

“You see?” Rio said with a smile on his lips.

“Fufu, even if I can’t see her, I can easily picture Ai-chan’s face right now.” Miharu also laughed in amusement. For the record, Aishia was currently within Rio’s body in her spirit form, but was able to telepathically communicate with Miharu when she was at an extremely close distance, thanks to their previous temporary contract. With Rio present, it meant the three of them could communicate with their minds.

Then, as the three of them continued to chat casually, they arrived at the gate before Liselotte’s mansion. Rio stopped around ten meters before the gate.

“This is Liselotte’s estate,” he said while looking at Miharu.

“I-It’s huge. I was thinking that while we were walking too.” Miharu stared at the outside of the mansion intently. The estate was enclosed in walls, but even without the walls it would have been impossible to see the entire grounds from their position. That was how large Liselotte’s estate was.

“She’s the daughter of a grand lord, and the president of a large merchant’s guild too. Considering how Amande wasn’t a large city to begin with, this would actually be a smaller property,” Rio explained to Miharu. Amande was still under development and continuously expanding, so if there was more spare land to begin with, the estate would have been much larger.

The two of them discussed such things by the gate when one of the gatekeepers approached them.

“Greetings. Do you have business with the mansion?” the male gatekeeper asked. Rio and Miharu weren’t hiding their bodies and faces with coats and hoods, so while their outfits were tidy, they clearly weren’t nobles and could have appeared to be suspicious. Miharu’s hair color was also altered with an artifact.

“My name is Haruto. I’ve come to request an audience with Lady Liselotte. If she is busy at the moment, then a future appointment would also suffice,” Rio stated respectfully.

“Sir Haruto... My apologies for not recognizing you. You are the same swordsman who saved my master when she was being attacked by monsters, correct?”

“I wouldn’t say I saved her outright, but...” Rio replied modestly with a wry smile.

“Then this girl... Are you Sir Haruto’s companion, if I may ask?” The gatekeeper looked at Miharu.

“Yes. Her name is Miharu Ayase.”

Rio gave Miharu’s full name, which made the gatekeeper think she was a noble from her last name. He widened his eyes and invited the two of them through the mansion gates. “...Understood. Then I shall first lead you to my master’s attendants, so please come this way. Hey, it’s Sir Haruto. Send a message to the mansion,” he said to the other soldiers at the gate. One of the soldiers ran towards the mansion to inform them of the situation first.

Rio and Miharu were then led through the gate and onto the estate. The garden of the estate was large and spacious, capturing Miharu’s gaze wherever she looked.

Then, once they reached the building, the front door opened to the attendants welcoming them. Cosette, Natalie, and Chloe appeared.

“Why, Sir Haruto, welcome to the estate.” Cosette took the lead to offer words of welcome, respectfully bowing her head. Natalie and Chloe did the same.

“Long time no see, everyone,” Rio replied to Cosette in a friendly manner. At that, Cosette raised her head and spotted Miharu for the first time, giving her a curious look. She didn’t voice any thoughts out loud.

“Yes, it’s a pleasure to be seeing you again. I’ve heard the situation. Please, come inside,” Cosette said brightly, inviting Rio and Miharu into the mansion.

“Thank you very much.” Rio bowed and followed Cosette’s lead inside.

“E-Excuse me,” Miharu also bowed awkwardly, following after Rio with timid steps.

“We’ll take over from here. Thank you,” Natalie said to the gatekeeper soldier upon their departure. The soldier promptly excused himself and returned to the mansion gate.

“I’m sorry for dropping by so suddenly, but I was hoping to at least secure an agreement for a future meeting,” Rio said to Natalie as they walked through the mansion.

Natalie shook her head. “No, you are our master’s savior, so we’ve been ordered to always welcome you with priority upon your visit. You may need to wait for a short while, but you should be able to meet her today, so allow us to lead you to the drawing room,” she replied warmly.

“...I am honored to hear that.” Rio smiled in embarrassment.

“This is the drawing room. Please, go on in.” Once Cosette had led them to the drawing room, she quietly opened the door and prompted them inside.

“Excuse me.” Rio allowed himself to be guided inside and sat on a chair. Miharu nervously sat beside him. Afterwards, tea was promptly brought out.

“Now, please wait a moment until my master arrives. We will be waiting outside the room, so please call for us if you need anything.” The attendants retreated from the room respectfully.

Once Miharu was alone with Rio, she took a deep breath to calm herself. “...I-I’m feeling really nervous all of a sudden.”

“It’ll be okay — I’m sure she’ll agree to you accompanying us. Just leave it to me,” Rio assured her readily, but it wasn’t an empty promise by any means. Even if Liselotte were to refuse, he had brought a means of negotiation along.

“I’m sorry. Even though this was my own selfish request, everything’s left to you again...” Miharu felt ashamed of her own worthlessness and apologized.

“I’m doing it because I want to. Don’t let it bother you,” Rio encouraged Miharu with a smile. At that moment, a knock came from the door. Rio and Miharu looked towards the door, which opened a few moments later.

“Sorry to keep you waiting, Sir Haruto.” The one who entered was the master of the estate, Liselotte. Behind her was her head attendant, Aria.

“It’s been a while, Liselotte.” Rio immediately stood up and placed his right hand on his chest respectfully as he greeted her.

“N-Nice to meet you. Thank you for having me here.” Miharu also stood up promptly and bowed her head somewhat uncomfortably.

“...Miharu Ayase, was it? My servant informed me of your name. It’s nice to meet you. I am Liselotte Cretia, the governor of the city of Amande.” Liselotte glanced at Miharu and burned her appearance into her memory before introducing herself with a sociable smile.

“Y-Yes. It’s an honor to be in your presence,” Miharu replied, gulping nervously.

“It seems like you have something to discuss today, so why don’t we all take a seat.” Liselotte invited them to take their seats with receptive ease.

Once Rio sat down, he immediately launched into their discussion. “I’m here to discuss what I mentioned before — the reason why I requested to attend the night banquet. It’s something that involves Miharu, so she came along for this.”

“If you would care to elaborate?” Liselotte calmly prompted him to continue, her expression remaining the same.

“Miharu is a friend of Satsuki Sumeragi, the hero that was summoned in Galarc Kingdom. With this much information, I’m sure you can infer the rest.”

Liselotte closed her eyes for a moment. “...Aria, please step outside for a moment. Wait outside the door and make sure no one comes in.”

“...Understood.” Aria nodded respectfully, departing from the room as ordered.

“I apologize for that. The truth is, the hero... Sir Sakata and Princess Flora are still here at the mansion, so it’s possible they may come here. I took the necessary means to prevent them from interrupting our conversation.”

“Thank you,” Rio bowed his head with a faint smile. Sakata Hiroaki was certainly likely to barge into a room without any consideration, which would be undesirable indeed.

“...Actually, from the moment I saw Miharu’s face, I had the impression her facial structure wasn’t one that I’ve seen within the neighboring kingdoms. However, that is not enough to prove that Miharu is from the same world as the hero. Sir Haruto’s testimony makes me lean towards the believing side, but if you don’t mind, may I speak to Miharu myself a little? I should be able to ascertain whether Miharu and the hero are from the same world.” Liselotte took a short but deep breath and stared straight at Miharu as she spoke.

“Ah, umm...” Miharu looked at Rio beside her and sought permission with her gaze. Rio nodded his approval at Miharu.

“Yes, I don’t mind,” said Miharu.

“Once again, it’s nice to meet you, Miharu. My name is Liselotte Cretia. I was a Japanese person in my past life. Can you understand what I’m saying?” Liselotte suddenly started speaking in Japanese. Her pronunciation was a little awkward, but it was definitely Japanese.

“Uh...” Miharu was taken aback with intense shock. She had never imagined that Liselotte would suddenly start speaking Japanese — and neither did Rio.

Chapter 8: Dreamland to Tomorrow

That night, Miharu had a dream.

With bleary awareness, she vaguely wondered where she was and what time it was. The sensation felt like one she had experienced just recently.

This is...

Right... This was a dream.

Contrary to Miharu’s bleary awareness, she was certain she could feel her mind stirring awake. Right now, in front of Miharu, a familiar boy and girl stood facing each other. Of course they would be familiar: the two were childhood friends, and the girl was Miharu herself. The boy was, of course, Amakawa Haruto.

Miharu watched her young self face Haruto in a daze.

This was when Haru-kun and I parted ways...

Miharu dug through her memories to identify the scene that was playing out in her dream. There was no mistaking it — the dream she was seeing now was a reenactment of a memory.

It had been one summer day. The sun’s rays scattered over them as the dream Miharu cried while desperately clinging to Haruto.

“Don’t go, Haru-kun!”

“Don’t cry, Mii-chan. We’ll meet again, okay?” In contrast to the bawling Miharu, Haruto was gallantly trying to cheer her up. It was so vexing and saddening to see, Miharu’s face fell into an expression of pain.

“I’ll come get you when we’re bigger! We’ll get married! That way... we’ll always be together, I’ll always be beside you, and I can protect Mii-chan with my life!” Haruto declared to Miharu, earnest and desperate.

“Yes... yes! I want to marry Haru-kun!” The young Miharu’s eyes sparkled fiercely as she hugged Haruto. It was a tender and fleeting promise made in their youth, with no binding power at all, but that was precisely why it felt so bright and precious to Miharu.

Mm...

Miharu couldn’t help the tears that welled in her eyes as she watched the scene. There had been no sadder day in her entire life than this one... And yet, at the same time, there hadn’t been a happier day, either.

That was why Miharu swore to be stronger and optimistic from that day onwards. As she grew older, the nature of her feelings changed, but the young Miharu blindly believed that one day Haruto would come to get her...

Huh?

The scene Miharu was looking at suddenly changed, like someone had switched television channels. Miharu’s eyes widened as she blinked. It was though she was looking at a collection of scenes in a compilation. Miharu wasn’t there, but Haruto was.

In the changing scenes that went by, Haruto was working his hardest in a variety of things. Studying, housework, farming, martial arts — he worked earnestly at all of them.

With that routine, Haruto slowly grew older bit by bit, and at some point, he reached the same age as the current Miharu. He was bowing his head at his father, asking to attend the same high school where he had once lived with Miharu.

Maybe... Maybe he remembered his promise with me? Miharu couldn’t help but wonder. Then, the scene changed once again.

This is... the high school I’m going to...?

Miharu gazed in shocked wonder at the new scenery before her. To her great surprise, the dream Haruto was standing there wearing the same school uniform as Miharu.

“...” On the campus with dancing sakura petals, Haruto was simply standing still, and his gaze was directed straight ahead of him. Miharu was lured into looking the same way.

Then, standing there — Oh...! — was Miharu.

Aki’s stepbrother — Sendo Takahisa — had called out to her, so the two of them were talking with familiarity.

This was during the entrance ceremony... Miharu was able to place the exact moment she was witnessing. Yes, there was no mistaking it — this happened on the day of the entrance ceremony. While it felt like many days had passed since then, it wasn’t actually that long ago, so her memories were still fresh. More than anything, that afternoon was the day she had wandered into this world, so the entrance ceremony was the only day Miharu wore her high school uniform.

Is this... really a dream? Miharu felt a strange sense of reality as the blood drained out of her face. Then, the dream Haruto who had been watching Miharu and Takahisa talk animatedly paused, before showing a small, sad smile.

Eh, ah... Perhaps what Haruto saw just now made him misunderstand Miharu and Takahisa’s relationship, making him think they were dating. No... but even if he didn’t misunderstand, the possibility could have risen in his head. Then, out of fear to confirm that—

Ah, w-wait!

Haruto turned on his heel. Miharu tried to call out to him, but her mouth wouldn’t move and the words didn’t come out. Even if she could think within this dream, she wasn’t able to interfere with the people that appeared. With no other choice, Miharu hurriedly followed after Haruto.

No, Haru-kun — wait, please!

Miharu desperately tried to cling to Haruto, but she wasn’t able to touch him. Haruto had a sad and uneasy smile on his face.

Seeing his side profile made Miharu’s chest tighten in pain. Then, the scene of the dream changed once again.

?!

This time, she saw inside the school building. Haruto was walking down the corridor, heading towards a certain classroom. Just how much time had passed since then?

“Is Ayase Miharu here yet?” Haruto asked some girls standing near the doorway of the classroom.

“Ah, umm. Ayase?” A quiet girl standing closest to the door looked frightened at suddenly being addressed.

“Ah, isn’t she the one who went absent without leave? You know, along with Sendo...” said a different girl.

“Absent without leave? But she was here for the entrance ceremony yesterday, right?” Haruto asked curiously.

“Right! There were rumors about that during the first break today. There has to be some deeper meaning to the two of them both going missing on the second day of school! The teacher didn’t know why either, so people were saying they must have eloped. Right?” One of the girls seemed to like gossiping, as she answered the question happily. In contrast, Haruto’s expression fell.

“I see... Thank you very much. Excuse me.”

“Ah, wait! What class are you fro... Hey!”

But Haruto left immediately. The girls tried to call out to him, but he wouldn’t stop for anyone.

Is this dream... what happened after I disappeared? Miharu thought, her face twitching. She felt a cold chill run down her spine. If that were the case, she was scared to imagine the future.

No... She didn’t want to see it. She didn’t want to see anything ahead of this. She was scared.

An indescribable fear ran through Miharu, making her want to flee... But she couldn’t. Even if she was scared, she had to see it. She didn’t have to say anything, at least; her existence wouldn’t be noticed. Even if this was in her dreams, she still wanted to stay by Haruto’s side, so Miharu resolved herself to watch to the end.

Time in the dream world continued ruthlessly. Before she knew it, dream-Haruto was attending university. He was saving a crying elementary school girl who had missed her bus stop, on his way home from campus himself.

...Huh? Miharu felt a strange sense of deja vu at the scene. If she recalled correctly, just recently —

Latifa said...

It was what had happened in Latifa’s past life. She had been an elementary school student who missed her bus stop on a rainy day, when Haruto saved her while she was crying.

It’s... raining...

It was pouring rain, Miharu confirmed.

Then this is one before...?

The two of them would die — Miharu remembered that and paled.

The next moment, the scene changed again. They were still on the bus, but Haruto’s outfit had changed.

?!

Haruto was swaying to the bus’ movements as he idly stared out the window. However, he suddenly noticed something and looked to his right rear. The elementary school girl Haruto had saved was sitting there.

“...?!” The elementary school girl had been staring fixedly at Haruto, but averted her eyes when she noticed him looking back. Haruto tilted his head with an unconvinced look. Miharu had been watching in a daze, but snapped out of it and reached for Haruto.

No, no, no, at this rate... no...!

But in the very next moment, the bus shook violently.

Haru-kun!

Miharu tried to hug Haruto’s body in a panic, but his body lightly flew through the air, hitting the roof of the bus.

The cause was a traffic accident from ignoring a red traffic light — the bus had been going through the green light when a truck suddenly collided from the left rear. The truck tried to avoid the bus by immediately turning the handle to the right, but it crashed into the left rear of the bus and sent it toppling over. The rear end of the bus was smashed to pieces — destroyed to the point where anyone sitting there would not have made it.

Ah, ah, aah...

Miharu was standing outside of the bus before she knew it, watching the tragic remains of the accident in a daze. She could hear the screams of the witnesses around the scene.

No... no no no noooo!

Unable to bear it, Miharu screamed in her dream.

“?!” Miharu woke up. The moment she did, she could feel her heart thumping and her lungs gasping for breath. “Hah, hah, hah...”

Her pajamas were soaked with sweat, and her heart was beating loudly enough to tear her chest open. Her body was so cold, it didn’t feel like she was alive. She couldn’t stop trembling.

“That... was a dream, right?” Miharu whispered.

Yes, a dream. It had to have been a dream.

It was just too tragic to be real.

Something like that was just— it was just—

Haruto— Haruto isn’t Haru-kun, right? It can’t be, it can’t, it can’t... Miharu said to convince herself, but her intuition was stating otherwise. It was so horrible, so sad; tears were streaming from her face before she knew it.

“Miharu.”

Aishia’s voice echoed in her ear from close by.

“Wha— A-Ai-chan...?! Why are you in my room...?” Miharu’s body shook as she answered. At some point, Aishia had appeared beside her.

“Do you want to forget the dream you just had, Miharu?” Aishia suddenly asked.

“...What— What are you saying, Ai-chan?” Miharu grimaced.

“If you want to forget that dream just now, I can make you forget it. The next time you sleep and wake up again, you won’t have any memories left of your dream. But if you don’t want to forget it, then the next time you wake up, you’ll still have those memories,” Aishia explained calmly. “Which would you prefer?”

“W-Which...” Miharu’s expression was on the verge of tears. Just what could she mean? Perhaps this in itself was another dream. Miharu was so confused, she wasn’t sure what was happening.

“Right now, Haruto has closed off his heart. There’s no more turning back for him, so he doesn’t want to drag the people that are precious to him into his affairs. That’s why, at this rate, Haruto will one day say goodbye to those very people. Miharu... you’re included among those people. That’s why Haruto is trying to distance himself,” Aishia continued.

“...” Miharu’s heart was stirred, panic showing across her face.

“But it’s not yet too late. Because Haruto’s way of thinking is wrong... It’s true that he may no longer be able to turn back. But if you want to follow Haruto willingly, then that’s your freedom to do so.” When Aishia said that, Miharu exhaled softly in relief.

“That’s why, if you strongly desire to stay by Haruto’s side, you mustn’t run away. Stand and face Haruto straight-on, and strongly express your will.” Aishia stared straight at Miharu.

“...Okay.” Miharu was nodding before she knew it.

“But there was something you had to know before you could express your will to Haruto. That was the dream just now. If you want to stay by Haruto’s side in the future, you’ll feel even worse than what you felt while seeing that dream. Haruto is proceeding down such a path. That’s why you needed to know that. If you don’t think you should be with him because of that, if you think you’d be better off away from him... Sorry, I interrupted your conversation with Haruto today.”

“What... What do you know, Ai-chan?” Miharu asked, who was frowning with a somewhat sad expression.

“I only know Haruto,” Aishia said, shaking her head with a slightly sad but warm smile.

“...” Miharu said nothing; she didn’t know how to respond. She had no idea what Aishia was feeling as she made such a face.

“You decide, Miharu. Do you still want to be by Haruto’s side, after seeing that dream?” Aishia asked calmly.

“Ah...” Miharu gulped.

“In the not-so-distant future, Haruto will come to tell you the truth. Your chance will be then. If you want to stay by Haruto’s side, you can’t run away. Not now, and not then,” Aishia said, reaching her hand out to pet Miharu’s cheek softly.

It’s cold... It was a hand that had no body temperature. And yet, for some reason...

...It’s warm. Somehow, Miharu was filled with a warm and fuzzy feeling.

“Hey, Ai-chan. Wait.” Miharu grasped Aishia’s hand tightly. There was no hesitation in her eyes.

“I... I... I want to be with Haru-kun,” she stated with firm resolution, but suddenly felt extremely sleepy.

“...Got it. It’ll be okay — I’m here. Good night, Miharu.” Aishia’s mouth turned upward in a gentle smile as she offered those final words.